SIDRA **SAJAD**

+923165424864



sidraabbasi478@gmail.com



Software Engineer

Tehsil Murree, District Rawalpindi, Pakistan.



OBJECTIVE

I am Sidra, a passionate Web Developer and dedicated self-learner. I've completed my Bachelor of Science in Computer Science (BSCS) from the Virtual University of Pakistan. I'm skilled in HTML, CSS, Bootstrap and JavaScript, and I am currently learning React.js to enhance my front-end capabilities. Additionally, I have experience in PHP and MySQL for backend development. With my diverse skill set, I am well-prepared to tackle complex projects and make meaningful contributions to the field of computer science.

EDUCATION

Virtual University of Pakistan

Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science 2021 – 2024

University of the Punjab

Bachelor of Science 2018 – 2021

SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- Bootstrap
- Tailwind CSS
- JavaScript
- React.js
- PHP
- MySQL
- Firebase

CERTIFICATIONS

- Web Development Course
- Frontend Development Bootcamp
- Freelancing course under DigiSkills Training Program
- Graphic Design course under DigiSkills Training Program

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Web Development Intern

CodXo | June 2024 - July 2024

Web Development Intern

CodeSoft | May 2024 - June 2024

Web Development Intern

BehinDev | April 2024 - May 2024

Computer Science Teacher

Cadet College Murree | April 2022 - June 2022

Computer & Math Teacher

APS Murree | March 2021 - June 2021

Junior Teacher

Murree Grammar Model School | May 2018 - Oct 2018

FINAL YEAR PROJECT

Online Bus Station And Ticketing System

Social Media Profiles

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/sidra-sajad-abbasi

GitHub

https://github.com/sidrasajad